The year is 1582.
Nobunaga Oda, who sought to
unify Japan, is murdered by
his own general, Mitsuhide Akechi,
before his dream is realized.
However, Hideyoshi Toyotomi,
Nobunaga's right-hand man,
defeats Mitsuhide.
Toyotomi's reign as Nobunaga's
successor is solidified.
The embers of conflict
continue to burn,
but the country is visited
by a temporary peace.
Stupid bastards!
Open the gates!
You are Bunzaemon Kinokuniya?
Yes.
By order of Lord Hideyoshi, we
have come to confiscate any items
left behind by the traitor
Mitsuhide Akechi.
Hand them over now!
I'm telling you, I have no
recollection of having met Akechi
nor of receiving
anything of his!
Check the storehouse.
We shall decide whether
any items are here.
"Go"
"Go" Thief! It's a thief!
Thief! It's a thief!
So...
This is here? Or this is here?
Then go through here, and
that leads out to...
Huh?
There he is! Get him!
Sasuke, you idiot. This is so
not what you said it would be!
Yeah, right.
You try and steal from a
public official like me?
That's not good.
Ah! It's Goemon!
Huh? Where?!
Oh! There!
Goemon!
Whoa. Now that's a sight!
That's!
Yeah. The greatest thief in the
world, and friend to the poor,
Goemon Ishikawa.
He's so awesome!
Hey!
Go! It's Goemon!
The heck? It's empty.
Do it up tonight!
Bastard! Get down from there!
You're under arrest!
Of course I ain't gettin'
down from here. Dumbass!
Later, guys.
Goemon! You're the
best in all Japan!
Say, Mr. Ishikawa...
Hm?
Will you finally take
one of them tonight?
Huh? I guess, but...
I got no money!
That's of no concern. I will
pay all your bills here.
That's a lovely thing.
Goemon!
I missed you so much! Say, Goemon,
tonight will be my turn, right?
You don't care for these
pissant little girls, do you?
Huh? I would be a far better
choice than you, of course.
Well, I'd take either of ya.
What are you looking at?
Okay! Shall we dance?!
It's not here. It must
have been that thief.
"Go"
Saizo.
Just who is he?
A thief who's been making a name
for himself around town recently.
He has the box. You must
get it back from him.
Sir.
Also...
Kill everyone in this house.
I'm sure you understand.
Women, children... Everyone.
I will visit Lord
Hideyoshi tomorrow.
He must know nothing of the box.
Understand?
Sasuke.
Washcloth.
Huh? How'd you know I was here?
It was obvious. Just hurry
up and give me one.
Okay, okay. You sure are
a slave driver. Here.
Gotcha.
Ow! Just what are
you doing, sir?!
It's obvious, fool.
What is?
Don't "What is?" me. This map.
It's completely wrong!
That caused me a lot
of trouble yesterday!
Huh? Oh, really?
There's yesterday's take.
Thank you, as always!
By the way, you're not still
gunning for me, are you?
Perish the thought! I thought you
were just a masterless samurai.
You beat me time and again.
Also...
I make so much money
being your ally!
That you do.
By the by, it seems last night's
mansion was no ordinary mansion.
Mitsunari Ishida of the
Five Commissioners
has apparently gone and seized it.
Something about a lacquered box...
It wasn't there, so they've been
raising hell in town looking for it.
So this lacquered box...
was it this big?
Probably.
And blue?
Uh-oh.
Yeah, I snatched it.
I knew it!
Why didn't you
tell me about it?!
I didn't know it was there either!
So, where is it?
I tossed it.
Thank goodness!
Every family member and servant
in that mansion was slaughtered!
It's just terrible.
Seems kinda interesting.
Huh?
I'm going. I'm gonna
look for that box.
Sir, that's a bad idea! Mitsunari
has put Saizo on the job!
The Saizo Kirigakure...
I ain't never heard of him.
In underworld circles, he's
the most infamous of shinobi.
They say he's fiercely talented. So,
let's not get too involved. Okay?
I'm going.
Well?
This box is from the Christian,
and it can play music.
Those buggers make one
interesting thing after another.
Mitsunari.
You seem busy lately.
Sir. All on your behalf, Lord.
On my behalf, huh?
Mitsunari... Just what're
you looking for?
Your meaning, sir?
Don't screw with me!
A box, isn't it?
A lacquered one.
Oh yes, Mr. Ishikawa. That
gentleman left this morning.
Is that so?
Say, Yashichi, I'm thirsty.
Bring me some water.
Yes, ma'am. Right... Huh?
An example?
Sir. The selling of any
lacquered goods is banned.
I believed your influence would
be weakened if we did nothing.
I saw to this matter myself. I
apologize for acting out of turn.
You are one of the
Five Commissioners,
appointed personally by me.
Do not act "out of turn."
If you go too far...
My lord! Lady
Chacha has arrived!
Ah! She's here, eh?
How fortunate for
you, Lord Ishida.
Lord Tokugawa. What do
you mean, "fortunate"?
I glimpsed Lady Chacha earlier.
Long had it been since I'd seen her.
She grows more and more beautiful.
One can see how Lord Hideyoshi
would become entranced.
Lady Chacha is the niece
of Lord Nobunaga.
Lord Hideyoshi was his
most trusted retainer.
No doubt she is as
if his daughter.
However...
Is that all, I wonder?
Farewell.
Chacha...
Following Lord Nobunaga's death,
I have acted as your father
for how many years now is it?
It has been 15 years since then.
What could I possibly
say to thank you?
What are you saying? I've
simply acted as I should...
If not for Lord Nobunaga, I would
have died still a poor farmer.
But now I am the great
Hideyoshi, the supreme ruler!
The ways of the world change...
Chacha, you must change, too.
Become my concubine.
Will you be my concubine
and bear me a child?
A child to continue the
Nobunaga bloodline...
Who is it?
I, Rikkyu.
Oh, my! Lord Hideyoshi!
I shall return later.
No. I was about to leave.
Rikkyu.
Sir.
Chacha will remain here in the
castle for the time being.
I await a favorable reply.
Such a long time it has
been, Lady Chacha!
You must be tired after
your long journey.
Ah, yes! I shall
bring you some tea.
Rikkyu...
My lady?
In this land...
Can one see fireflies
in this land?
Come on, please wait, sir!
How are you going to look for
it in the midst of all this?
Instinct, I guess.
I thought it'd be
something like that.
C'mon, Mom. Eat.
Koheita, this...
What, you think I stole it?
I saw Goemon yesterday!
What about you?
I ate earlier, so I'm okay.
C'mon, eat.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Mom! Are you all right? Hold on.
I'll buy you some medicine.
Hey.
It stinks! This is where
the absolute poorest live.
Since they opened
up the free market,
it's well and good for
those who make it...
but this is what happens
to all the weak ones.
It's brought riches, but
it's brought disparity, too.
"The strong devour
the weak," huh?
Whether that's good or not...
Right, sir?
There you go. There, there.
You don't plan on
searching, do you?
That ain't it at all.
Mom!
- Is this all right?
- Mom!
- It's fine.
Scum like this are
a dime a dozen.
Who are you, bastard?
If you don't want your prized sword
cutting of that head of yours,
then get the hell out of here.
Bro!
Sir!
Hurry!
Sir, that was going too far!
Mom... Mom! Why? Why?
Because you're weak.
You thought that, didn't you? You can't win.
You'll be killed.
That this wouldn't have happened
if you were stronger than them.
Am I wrong?
Become stronger, boy. Then
nothing can be taken from you.
I'm borrowing this box.
Okay! We've got the box, so
let's get out of here, sir!
It's too late.
What's with him?
It's Saizo.
Huh? Huh?!
Goemon.
You will give me the box.
And what if I say "No"?
You'd do well not to say that.
Sir! Sir!
What's with you.
It's just a joke.
Fine. Here it comes.
Come with me!
See you.
After him.
Hey, that's dangerous!
Alrighty then!
Move, move, move!
Sir!
Seems you haven't
gotten soft yet.
"Through the land"
You're quite determined. Just
what is it with that box?
It's Pandora's Box.
The heck is that?
It's a legend from the
West, a box that,
if opened, will invite calamity.
Do it.
What about the box?
Circumstances have changed.
You've narrowly escaped death.
Sir! Are you all right?!
Delicious!
If you ain't eatin',
I'm takin' it.
Hey! Sir, are we really
bringing this kid along?
Where's the harm?
Harm or no, he'll
just get in the way!
We have a job that requires our
sacred, nay, divine capabilities!
What can this little shit do?
Look, it's not much different
if one burden becomes two.
Yeah, but still...
Hey, that includes me!
Aah, I'm full!
Now then...
What is that? That box.
It's the Pan-something Box.
By the way, sir...
Saizo is an
acquaintance of yours?
Why?
I got that feeling somehow.
Well, we're both famous.
Please don't try to fool me.
This bugs you?
This bugs me. You don't tell me
a single thing about your past!
I first had sex at 15.
I'm not asking about that!
I'm just a thief. The greatest thief
in the world, Goemon Ishikawa.
That should be enough.
What are these?
What is it?
It's like a map.
What's with you? You're so loud.
Here.
- Thanks for the food.
- Sir!
Let's go.
Thankya!
The bill.
Here... It's here, right?
Yeah.
This.
It's inside this thing's ear.
I've got something.
Ow! Ow! Ow! I'm stuck!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Sir! Sir, please help!
Sir, please look!
What's this?
Sir! Sir!
Ow...
A jointly sealed document?
Huh? I think I've seen
these crests somewhere...
Come out. You've followed us all
the way from the restaurant.
Y-Yeah! You've totally been obvious.
Who the hell are you?
Hanzo Hattori.
Um... Hanzo Hattori?!
I'm giving this back.
Who is he?
Everyone knows of him, but no
one has seen him and lived!
He's a legendary shinobi. Shit!
What do you want?
I want to buy that document.
If that's not enough,
I'll get more.
There's no way we'd sell it
for chump change like that!
Fine. I'll sell it.
That's right! Huh?
You're selling it?
If you are out of work,
I know a good employer.
I got no problem gettin' food.
Hey.
Is that thing real?
What was that? Hanzo?!
Possibly at leyasu's command.
That conniving old bastard!
So he knows of the document?
If Goemon gave him the box...
Shit! We finally had our
trump card in hand!
Who the hell is this
"Goemon" anyway?!
My. Such a scary face.
It won't be much longer. If we
can just get that document.
If we have that...
Still, I feel like I've seen
those crests somewhere...
Where was it?
Huh? Huh?
Hey, brat. Have you
seen my short sword?
How would I know about
that stupid thing?
It's not stupid.
Hey, where's Goemon?
Huh? Oh.
He's sleeping, oddly enough.
You hurry and sleep too, brat.
Stupid brat!
Did you get it?
Fall back.
I remember!
What?
Those crests. They're of the
Akechi and Hashiba clans!
The crests on the document!
Akechi? Hashi?
Yes. Akechi as in Mitsuhide Akechi.
The man who, 15 years ago,
betrayed Lord Nobunaga as he
was about to unify Japan,
assassinating him
at Honno Temple.
Who's Hashiba?
Hashiba is Hideyoshi Hashiba, the
former name of Hideyoshi Toyotomi.
It can't be...
So Hideyoshi and Mitsuhide
were secretly aligned.
What does that mean?
It means Lord Hideyoshi himself
planned Nobunaga's assassination.
This document is valuable
proof of that fact.
So, will he act?
Possibly.
Sir! Sir! This isn't
the time for sleeping!
Bastard! Who are you?
Lord Nobunaga's... avenger!
What is the matter?!
Who are you?
Goemon!
Lady Chacha.
Chacha!
Old woman.
Wandering around these parts
at night is dangerous.
They say bandits come out.
Please, sir! The child!
Spare the child! Please!
We got no use for a
wrinkled-up hag like you.
On the other hand...
You're a cute little
thing, aren't you?
I could sell you for plenty.
You little shit!
Boy. Become stronger. Then
nothing can be taken from you.
Will you come with me? I
will make you strong.
Welcome back, Lord Nobunaga.
Lord Nobunaga,
what of the child?
As of today, he is in my care.
Hanzo!
A new shinobi.
His name?
Goemon.
That all right?
Goemon. Saizo.
The winner gets to drink.
The shinobi are shadows.
Shadows have no need for self.
Destroy the self. Be only
a sword for your master.
Never expose yourself. Hide
yourself to the world.
That is the fate of the shinobi.
Enough. Stop.
Those two have
exceptional skill.
So my eyes did not deceive me.
Goemon!
Goemon.
You shouldn't get up yet.
Delish!
Today's newspaper.
Apparently someone murdered
Lord Hideyoshi's double.
On the night you took my
sword and disappeared...
then came back all injured.
Just who are you?
The greatest thief in the...
That's not enough!
A shinobi assigned
directly to Nobunaga Oda.
Now just a thief, huh?
That man brought you here.
Nobody friggin' asked him to.
Mitsunari!
Guarding this castle
is whose job?!
It's my job, sir!
Guarding the castle is left to
you, but your worthlessness
resulted in my
almost being killed!
Do you... want me... to die?
Not at all, sir!
Is that so?
Perhaps... just a
little too bitter.
Ah. That is a most pretty fan.
Were you perhaps visited
by an old acquaintance?
Rikkyu...
Madam?
Rikkyu, why are you in
Lord Hideyoshi's retain?
When I serve tea for great
men, such as Lord Hideyoshi,
I hear a voice.
A voice.
The voice of those
who move the world.
It was Lord Nobunaga
who taught me that.
Goemon!
Sir!
This is my niece, Chacha.
As of today, she is staying
here in the castle.
You will protect her.
Father... Mother...
Don't go.
Father!
Goemon... Goemon!
I'm here.
I had a scary dream.
I am here. Please rest easy.
Goemon?
Yes.
Where are your
father and mother?
I have none.
Oh. Then we're the same.
My father died in battle. Even now...
I dream of that time.
Over and over again.
And friends?
Do you have friends?
Yes. Just one.
What's his name?
His name is Saizo.
I hope I can make
friends someday, too.
I thought you would be bored,
always being inside the castle.
But it would not be good if
Lord Nobunaga learned of this.
Goemon?
Yes.
Do you think we've
become friends?
Thanks to you, I no
longer have scary dreams.
Here.
Thank you for everything.
Goodbye.
Goemon.
I am here.
As thanks for Chacha.
Have you gotten stronger?
I... still don't know.
That's good enough.
What's that? Lord Nobunaga?!
Mitsuhide Akechi rebelled.
At Honno Temple.
So it's done.
Good work. Sorry, but I will
take control of everything.
Lord Nobunaga!
Mitsunari Ishida?
Become his underlings?
Lords Hideyoshi and Mitsunari
were both born poor farmers.
But they came this far, high
enough to control everything.
So some day, even we should
be able to become samurai.
I'm fine.
I want to try being free.
A farewell gift.
"Through the land"
"Spread militarism"
What became of your sword?
I threw it away.
I won't say "Thank you."
I don't need it. It would be
unpleasant coming from you.
If Hideyoshi were simply killed,
the world would go back
to fighting and chaos.
Wars would erupt and many
innocent civilians would die.
So what? I'm free
to do what I like.
If you hadn't stolen the box, that
boy's mother wouldn't have died.
If you enjoy your freedom,
stop getting others involved.
Simply living without
purpose isn't being free.
You know that, don't you?
And what about you?! The henchman
for an idiot boss, worked hard
and hands stained with blood.
Just a little more...
Just a little more, and I can
become a samurai. And then...
Sheeit. This got wet.
For an unpopular guy,
you give long sermons.
I have a wife and child.
I feel bad for your wife.
Indeed...
I doubt we'll meet again.
If we do...
I'll kill you.
Hey.
That clothing really suits you.
You should change jobs.
You're way too flashy.
Being a thief...
The greatest thief.
Don't toot your own horn.
Rikkyu... Is it true
that war will begin?
Why would you say that?
I hear them, too. The voices.
Not war... No matter
what, war must not...
I understand. That is
why this current plan
must be prevented at all costs.
It is far too reckless.
Then Lord Hideyoshi and I...
No! If you do that, you would
consent to Lord Hideyoshi
and become his concubine.
Please leave this to me.
After all,
tea cannot be served if
the world is in turmoil.
In which case, I would
have nothing to do.
Look. Yes, that's it. It spun!
Everyone, thank you for gathering.
There's something I want you to see.
I do not care for the Christians. But
while they call their work "missions,"
the weapons they secretly
possess are outstanding.
This was an expensive purchase. I
want to mass produce these at once,
and attack Korea and China!
I will show you something else.
You should have just...
stuck to serving tea.
He found fault with my dream...
I will send my soldiers!
No, I will!
Kato, give soldiers.
Onishi, give supplies.
And I, sir?
Mitsunari? I didn't
notice you there.
Now then, everyone... It's war!
The boss sure is a slave driver.
Sasuke, you want to
be an official, too?
Huh?
An official. You want to
be someone important?
Well, of course! Listen,
people like us aren't suited
for commerce or rice planting.
But as long as we're not officials,
that's all we'll ever have. Ever!
So anyone would jump at the chance.
Let's see...
Yukimura Sanada's employ
would be pretty good, huh?
Then I'd buy a mansion, get
some girls, find a bride...
Or maybe get the bride first!
Ah, you ain't even listening.
Koheita.
Hey, what is it?
Idiot! Don't!
Rikkyu is?
His death is a great loss.
There is something I
wish to show you.
I'm back. Open up.
What is it, Okichi?
I... will kill Hideyoshi.
If that... if that
will stop this war.
You're truly fine with this?
Yes. However, I
have one request.
Sasuke sure is takin' his time.
Getting drunk?
Took you a long time to notice.
This isn't a place to
come to with another guy.
Indeed.
That is... far too reckless.
Please reconsider.
Shut up!
But...
I'll give you 200.
That's right. You'll
have your own salary.
With that, you can join
the ranks of the samurai.
That's what you want, isn't it?
No?
This is the only way.
The only one.
So you weren't harmed? I'm glad.
Here.
How many years has it
been since we came here?
Nothing has changed, has it?
Lady Chacha...
I...
Goodbye. I came to
tell you goodbye.
Lady Chacha will officially become
Lord Hideyoshi's concubine.
Take care of yourself.
In three days, a celebration will
be held on Lord Hideyoshi's boat
for the dispatching
of the troops.
That will be Lady Chacha's
introduction as his concubine.
Ieyasu Tokugawa...
What are you after?
"Through the land"
"Spread militarism"
My song will be the signal.
Avenge Lord Nobunaga!
That is the only way
to save Lady Chacha.
Sir. You've been out late.
What happened?
Son of a bitch!
Hey! Hey!
That's what happened.
So did he die?
I became stronger.
I became strong and I killed him.
I frickin' killed him!
Sir!
Sir! Please stop.
Get over there!
Hey!
Listen. This ain't what
your mother wanted!
Would your mom say to avenge her?
To kill someone?
She wouldn't want revenge!
What do you think? A
spectacle, isn't it? Look.
Look how many men have assembled.
For me and for you.
Excuse me.
Good work, everyone.
Does anyone need water?
Won't anyone sing? Well?
You're no fun.
I shall.
Ah, Lord Tokugawa. Very well.
♪ To think that a man
has but 50 years... ♪
That's right. Kill him.
Do it in front of everyone. News of
Hideyoshi's death will go public,
and the world will again
be plunged into war.
If we take advantage of that chaos,
the one closest to taking control...
will be you.
♪ ... a vain dream...  ♪
Give me your fan.
♪ To think that a man
has but 50 years... ♪
♪ To think that a man has but ♪ ♪
50 years to live under heaven... ♪
One day, I will put an
end to the fighting.
I will create a world
without fighting!
I dance for that day...
Don't let others call the steps!
Dance!
"She wouldn't want
revenge," huh?
I said those words.
What's happening?!
This way!
Good work.
Come on!
I'm alive!
I can't go.
Please go, Goemon.
That shinobi... is still alive.
Please go.
Please go!
Wait! Don't kill him. Make him say...
who hired him.
Say nothing if you value
your family's lives.
How dare you attack
Lord Hideyoshi?!
Do you know?
Apparently, he's at Sonezaki.
Sir, please don't. Saizo surely
prepared himself for this.
What's your name? Huh?
Speak!
If you help him... things
will get very difficult.
Just think of it as fate.
Do you really get it?!
Yeah.
I get it.
We meet again.
Don't kill me.
What? He escaped? You
will get him back!
I believe you already know, but...
bring him alive.
Sir! This is bad!
What is it? They found us here?
No!
They're going after...
Saizo's family!
What is it?
I told you! I said things
would get difficult!
Okichi! Okichi!
Saizo!
Look! This is the
freedom you spoke of!
This is the price to
pay for your freedom!
"Come to the castle if you
value your child's life."
Please move. Please move!
Well? Just tell me your name.
Do that, and at least your
child's life will be spared.
Hey!
Saizo!
Please move.
Hey! Hey!
My name is...
My name is... Goemon!
That's Goemon?
That's right! I am...
the world's greatest
thief, Goemon Ishikawa!
Stop it!
I've done so many bad things.
I've had a fun, interesting life.
I thought I'd kill Lord Hideyoshi
and go down in history,
but that's luck for you.
I'm Goemon! I'm Goemon Ishikawa!
Still...
Move!
How nice of you all
to gather here.
Now that's a sight!
You all!
You wondering why I tried to snuff
Lord Hideyoshi? You want to know?
Just look at this world!
Isn't it insane?!
Time after time, guys appear
seeking absolute power,
killing each other, spilling blood.
And they all say the same thing:
"This is the last time."
But that promise hasn't been
kept once, has it? Well?!
Stop it, Saizo.
And whose blood
gets spilled first?
It's your blood, isn't it?!
That's enough! Saizo!
Everyone, remember
this sight forever!
Stop it!
This is Goemon Ishikawa's
final performance!
You're lonely by yourself, huh?
How many times did I tell you?
"Stop it"?
How many times did I tell you
things would get difficult?!
I can't stay with you anymore.
Mitsunari.
Sir.
That shinobi earlier... he
told me his name was "Saizo."
That's your shinobi, isn't it?
Hey! What the hell
are you doing?
There must be some mistake. I
did not know that individual.
"Spread militarism"
Has Goemon arrived?
Don't take all the
glory for yourself.
You are not the only
one who mourns Saizo.
Let us handle this.
You go on ahead.
Fine.
Just don't die.
So you've made
your move, Goemon.
Now then, shall he or Lady
Chacha strike Hideyoshi first?
I thought you agreed to be
my concubine quite suddenly.
This is why?
For what you did
to Lord Nobunaga!
Yeah... I've gotta settle
things with you, huh?
The same trick won't work twice.
I see. So that document
still remained?
Mitsuhide Akechi was no fool.
However...
If you kill me, then what?
You want to return us
to a time of strife?
The war will not end.
No matter how much time
passes, nothing will change.
So you're finally here.
It's been a long time.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I've come to take you to hell.
Well, before that...
how about a drink?
A nice view, isn't it?
It is. That's why I
built this here.
What did it feel like?
Controlling everything.
It was quite good. Not as
good as this sake, though.
Why did you kill Lord Nobunaga?
You were his top subordinate.
I was hungry.
As you know, I was
born a poor farmer.
Since I was a child, I've been
so hungry that I can't stand it.
Just once, I wanted
to feel full.
That's why I strove to meet
Nobunaga's unreasonable demands,
working and moving upward.
But no matter how much I
ate, it wasn't enough.
No matter how much time passed,
I stayed hungry. Famished.
So, finally, I wanted to
try eating everything.
That's all there is to it.
Have any last words?
How did it feel, to be free?
You fled 15 years ago. To be free,
you fled from your own destiny.
So, did you find it?
Did you become free?
Go on. Do it.
You can't flee anymore.
Not from your destiny.
So Mitsunari has already
raised the troops?
Is it war?
No. Just a competition. For
the bait called "power."
We possess authority!
This document proves
that leyasu Tokugawa
is the rightful successor
to Lord Nobunaga!
With Hideyoshi Toyotomi dead,
who else but Lord leyasu
must restore order
to the world?!
I leave the rest to you.
Is it to avenge a friend?
Loyalty to a benefactor?
They wouldn't want that.
Take this.
Please... Please be
sure to come back.
Move out!
Drive them back.
That's a terrible thing
you've got there.
I'm going, too!
Say...
Do you know this story?
A girl gets curious and opens a
box that shouldn't be opened.
What are you talking about?
All kinds of disasters
are inside that box.
Disease, war, hatred... they come
flying out, plaguing people.
But the girl didn't let
one last thing out.
Thanks to that, humanity wasn't wiped out.
Do you know what it was?
What was it?
Something I'd lost.
Become strong, Koheita.
A lot stronger than me.
Lord Nobunaga?
I bring news! Lord Nobunaga...
Lord Nobunaga has
joined the fighting!
What idiocy is this?
Make no moves!
Have you gone mad?
Move aside!
If it weren't for you all...
This never ends because
you're fighting for power!
No one can be happy!
We are fighting for
that happiness as well!
I'm tired of hearing
things like that!
Ieyasu...
Swear that this is the end!
Swear that this will
end the fighting!
Swear that everyone can
live in happiness!
Goemon!
I got the man who tried to
strike down Lord leyasu!
I did it! It was my doing!
I did it! By my hands!
Hey! I did it! Hey!
Where's my reward?
Where's my reward?!
Tears from heaven, eh?
We must finish this.
Now that's a sight...